

Carlos García

JOB TITLE

□ carlos.garcia@gnail.com

- +99 699999988
- ♥ London, England
- in linkedin.com/carlos-garcia

OBJECTIVE

Proactive individual with more than 2000 url's completed over 5 year in several IT departments. My experience is based in the development of highly complex web pages for private companies and publics institutions. My work quality is reflected as a finalist 5 times for the "ESANDI" awards, winning twice.

SKILLS

- Communication
- Phyton
- Java script
- Experiencie speaking at events

LANGUAGES

- English: fluent
- Spanish: native speaker
- French: beginner level

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB Developer - Inditex

2023 - Present

- Develop well-structured, maintainable code and thoroughly test your own work.
- Monitor ongoing performance of web applications and infrastructure online.
- Assist the Head of IT in assessing security of web applications and action requerid changes arising from 3rd party pen testing of systems.

WEB Developer - Penguin Random House

2020 - 2023

- Work within browser team to lead technical community.
- Engage with developers, for example on social media, in order to learn about their needs and gather feedback.
- Speak at and organise developer events both virtual and physical (travel will be a part of this role).

Database Administrator – Computer Center

2019 - 2020

- Work within browser team to lead technical community.
- Engage with developers, for example on social media, in order to learn about their needs and gather feedback.

EDUCATION

WEB Development MASTER'S - University of Liverpool 2011 – 2013

Computer Engeeniring DEGREE – Keele University 2007 - 2010

REFERENCES

Andrés PRYM

Director

INDITEX Textile Design Industry 135 Heygate St, London, England +999 9999 9999 andres.prym@gnail.com

Sara COOPER

Head of HR Resources
PENGUIN RANDOM HOUSE
Garden Row, London, England
+999 9999 9999
sara.cooper@gnail.com